<form>
    <field>
        <id>router.address</id>
        <label>Address</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Hostname or IP address of the OpenWrt router.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <width>16em</width>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.hostname</id>
        <label>Hostname</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Display name for this router. Used as a label throughout the UI.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <width>14em</width>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.description</id>
        <label>Description</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Optional notes about this router (location, role, etc.).</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.ssh_username</id>
        <label>SSH username</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Username for SSH connections to this router. Leave as 'root' unless you have configured a dedicated SSH user on the router.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <visible>false</visible>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.ssh_key_ref</id>
        <label>SSH public key</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Select the firewall SSH public key that should be authorized on this router. Use 'Copy Public Key' to copy it to the clipboard, then add it to /root/.ssh/authorized_keys on the router.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <visible>false</visible>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.sync_wifi_config_from</id>
        <label>Sync Wi-Fi config from</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Select another router of the same hardware model to use as the Wi-Fi config source. When synced, this router's /etc/config/wireless will be overwritten with the source's content.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <visible>false</visible>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.sync_system_config_from</id>
        <label>Sync system config from</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Select another router of the same hardware model to use as the system config source. When synced, /etc/config/system will be overwritten from the source — except the hostname, which is always preserved from this router.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <visible>false</visible>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.sync_firewall_config_from</id>
        <label>Sync firewall config from</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Select another router of the same hardware model to use as the firewall config source. When synced, /etc/config/firewall will be overwritten with the source's content.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <visible>false</visible>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.sync_dhcp_config_from</id>
        <label>Sync DHCP config from</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Select another router of the same hardware model to use as the DHCP config source. When synced, /etc/config/dhcp (dnsmasq settings) will be overwritten with the source's content.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <visible>false</visible>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.sync_rpcd_config_from</id>
        <label>Sync authentication config from (rpcd)</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Select another router of the same hardware model to use as the rpcd config source. rpcd controls LuCI and ubus access control (users, roles, permissions). When synced, /etc/config/rpcd will be overwritten with the source's content.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <visible>false</visible>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.sync_status</id>
        <label>Config Source</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>The configured config sync source(s) and whether this router's configs currently match the source.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <width>16em</width>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.status</id>
        <label>Status</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Live health status from the last broker poll: Healthy, Warning, or Critical based on CPU load, memory, and disk usage.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <width>10em</width>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.version</id>
        <label>Version</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>OpenWrt firmware version detected from the last broker poll.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <width>10em</width>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>router.hardware</id>
        <label>Hardware</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Hardware model detected from the last broker poll.</help>
        <grid_view>
            <width>16em</width>
        </grid_view>
    </field>
</form>
